Guide to the Preservation Pittsburgh Records, 1985-2005 AIS.2005.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Civic Arena Demolition and Hill District Redevelopment, 2007-2013; V.
  - New Arena Master Plan, Focus Groups and Meetings, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania Grant Contract, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Historic Museum Commission Mitigation Recommendations, Correspondence, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Pittsburgh Penguins Arena Traffic Impact Study, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Preservation Pittsburgh Response to Criteria of Effect, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Robert Pfaffman, "A Civic Renewal" Presentation, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Summary of Memorandum of Agreement, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Community Benefits Agreement (CBA) - Draft, Changes, and Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - One Hill CBA Coalition - Meeting Minutes, Research, Correspondence, Notes, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - One Hill CBA Coalition - General Meeting, July, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - One Hill CBA Coalition - General Meeting, April, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2007-2011 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Mary Conturo, SEA Correspondence, 2007-2011 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Preservation Pittsburgh, Press Releases, Statements, and Campaign Materials, 2007-2011 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Press, 2007-2013 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hill Community Development Corporation Presentation, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Recycle the Igloo, Organizational Meeting, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Robert Pfaffman, "The Pittsburgh Civic Arena: Memory and Renewal", 2008 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - "A Civic Renewal: An Economic Benefits Prospectus for Reuse of the Civic Arena", 2010 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - "A Civic Renewal," Presentation, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Preservation Pittsburgh, Historic Hill Institute Presentation, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Reuse the Igloo, Campaign Materials, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Reuse the Igloo, Members Files, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Lower Hill (Mellon Arena) Redevelopment Interested Parties Meeting #1, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Lower Hill (Mellon Arena) Redevelopment Interested Parties Meeting #2, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Lower Hill (Mellon Arena) Redevelopment Interested Parties Meeting #3, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Lower Hill (Mellon Arena) Redevelopment Interested Parties Meeting #6, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Lower Hill (Mellon Arena) Redevelopment Interested Parties Meeting #7., 2010 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Preservation Pittsburgh, Correspondence and Testimony to City Government, 2010-2011 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Bill No. 2011-1611, Information and Public Hearing (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - District 6 Quarterly Newsletter, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Reuse the Igloo, Preservation Pittsburgh Meeting, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - August Wilson House, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - August Wilson House, Photos, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - "Civic Arena Facts" Presentation, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Civic Arena Postcard, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Coloring Book Sheets of Civic Arena Concept Drawing, undated (Box 7, Folder 42-43)
  - Edward G. Mitchell, Historical Presentation on the Civic Arena, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Maps, Concept Drawings, and Renderings of Civic Arena Reuse, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Portion of Civic Arena Historic Designation Nomination, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Preservation Pittsburgh, "Civic Arena Briefing Book", undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Reuse the Igloo, Historic Review Commission Meeting, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)